Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Loan files, 1930-2014; Series 11
  - Loans returned: Sully, Thomas - Sully's Daughter as a Character from Shakespeare's "The Nun", circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 105)
  - Loans returned: Donald Sultan - Detroit October 31, 1986, 1989 June 1; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 106)
  - Loans returned: Suzuki, James - Eccehomo, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 107)
  - Loans returned: Suzuki, James - Here Comes the Sun, Coral, 1967 May 1; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 108)
  - Loans returned: Heda, Willem, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 109)
  - Loans returned: Tobey, Mark - The Paratrooper, 1966 July 11; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 110)
  - Loans returned: Trumbull, John - Portrait of his Nephew, John M. Trumbull, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 111)
  - Loans returned: Kimio Tsuchiya, 1991 January 10; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 112)
  - Loans returned: Tapestry, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 113)
  - Loans returned: U, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 114)
  - Loans returned: Unidentified Am. Colonial Artist - Lewis Morris, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 115)
  - Loans returned: Unidentified American - Windsor Settee, 1977 August 26; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 116)
  - Loans returned: Van Aelst, Willem, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 117)
  - Loans returned: Vanderlyn, John - Theodosia Burr, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 118)
  - Loans returned: Van Der Sluis, George - Color Bar, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 119)
  - Loans returned: Vickrey, Robert - Rocky Landscape, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 120)
  - Loans returned: Vincente, Esteban - Comestock, 1968 October 8; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 121)
  - Loans returned: Secretary, 1968 May 1; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 122)
  - Loans returned: Vlaminck - Flowers, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 123)
  - Loans returned: Vonnoh, Bessie Potter - Julia Marlowe Taber, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 124)
  - Loans returned: Vonnoh, Bessie Potter - Julia Marlowe Taber, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 125)
  - Loans returned: Corner Tables - French, c. 1770, 1997 July 18; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 126)
  - Loans returned: Watkins, Franklin - Red Flowers in Blue Pitcher, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 127)
  - Loans returned: Waugh, Frederick - Open Sea, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 128)
  - Loans returned: Wechter, Vivienne - Ariadne's Thread, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 129)
  - Loans returned: Weiman, Adolph - Descending Night, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 130)
  - Loans returned: Weinman, Adolph - Rising Sun, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 131)
  - Loans returned: Weisz, Eugen - Limestone Head, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 132)
  - Loans returned: Wesselman, Tom - Great American Nude #65, 1968 January 19; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 133)
  - Loans returned: West, Benjamin - Cupid Stung by a Bee, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 134)
  - Loans returned: West, Benjamin - Telemachus and Calypso, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 135)
  - Loans returned: Wyeth, Jamie - Forced Landing, 1999 October 15; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 136)
  - Loans returned: Replica of Hungarian Crown, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 137)
  - Loans returned: Whistler, J.A.M. - Marine Scene, 1968 June 21; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 138)
  - Loans returned: Wiley, William T. - Battle Hymn, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 139)
  - Loans returned: Winner, William - Anne and Mary Jones, Daughters of Caleb Jones, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 140)
  - Loans returned: Zerbe, Karl - The Hex, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 141)
  - Loans returned: Zerbe, Karl - Tundra, 11 P.M., circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 142)
  - Loans returned: Zerbe, Karl - The Owl, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 143)
  - Loans returned: Zorach, William - Reclining Woman, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 144)
  - Loans returned: Weinman, Adolph, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 145)
  - Loans returned: Woodville, Richard, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 146)
  - Loans returned: Wollaston, John, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 147)
  - Loans returned: Unknown Artist, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 148)
  - Loans returned: Unknown American School, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 149)
  - Loans returned: Unknown Artist, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 150)
  - Loans returned: Unknown Artist, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 151)
  - Loans returned: Untitled, circa 1930-1990; Series 11 (Box 88, Folder 152)
  - Requests withdrawn: Mobile Museum of Art, 2007; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Unprocessed Loan Requests, 2001-2002; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Cancelled by venue: Jeu de Paume - Larry Rivers - Self Figure, Packing the Dutch Masters, The Auction, 2002 March 22; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Cancelled by venue - New Orleans Museum of Art - Jefferson's America and Napoleon's France - Gilbert Stuart - Mrs. Thomas Lea, 2002 July 31; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Loan requests declined, 2002 September 18; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Loan requests declined, 2002 December 30; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Requests Withdrawn, 2003-2004; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Loan Cancelled: PAFA - Charles Demuth - In Vaudeville: Bicycle Rider, 2003 January 21; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Cancelled by Venue: Tennessee State Museum - Retrospective Exhibition on Eleanor Creekmore Dickinson - Guide Me, O Thou Great Jehovah, Nearer My God to Thee, On Jordan's Stormy Bank I Stand, 2003 March; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Loans Declined, 2003 March 5; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Cancelled by Venue: Lenox Library Association - Hiram Powers - Anna Barker Ward, 2003 May 15; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Loan requests declined, 2003 September; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Loan requests declined, 2003 December; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Loan requests declined, 2004 March 10; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Loan requests declined, 2004 May 5; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Loan requests declined, 2004 September 22; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Loan requests declined, 2004 November 17; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Postponed: Katonah Museum - Kay Sage - Finger on the Drum - Postponed Until Further Notice, 2008, 2005 May 12; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Loan requests declined, 2005 March 2; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Loan requests declined, 2005 May 4; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Cancelled by venue: Telfair Museum of Art - Kent, Adirondacks, Lichtenstein, Bull Head I, II, and III, Melchers, Penelope, 2005 July; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Loan requests declined, 2005 September 8; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Loan requests declined, 2005 November 10; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Loan requests declined, 2006 February 28; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Loan requests declined, 2006 April 6; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Loan requests declined, 2006 September 25; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Unprocessed Loan Requests, 2003-2006; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Incomplete Loan Requests and Inquiries, 2006; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - Loan requests declined, 2006 November 9; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Loans Withdrawn, 2006; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - Loans Withdrawn, 2007; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - Loan requests declined, 2007 February 13; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - Loan requests declined, 2007 April 23; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - Loan requests declined, 2007 June 18; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - Loan requests declined, 2007 September 30; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 35)
  - Loan requests declined, 2007 November; Series 11 (Box 109, Folder 36)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Wollaston, Colonel Abraham Barnes - Historical Society Western Pennsylvania, Canadian War Museum, SI International Gallery, 2005 May 1-2007 July 15; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Eugene Delacroix, Tiger and Snake - Van Gogh Museum, Amsterdam, Carnegie Museum of Art, Pittsburgh, 2005 October 5-2006 August 27; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Pablo Picasso, Un Verre Sur la Table - Albuquerque Museum, Salvador Dali Museum, 2005 December 18-2006 July 30; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Sargent, Mrs. Henry White - NTL Gallery London, MFA Boston, The Met, NY, 2006 February 22-2007 January 28; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Frans van Mieris, The Lesson - National Gallery of Art, 2006 February 26-May 21; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Richard Norris Brooke, A Pastoral Visit - Palmer Museum, Boston Atheneum, 2006 March 6-2006 October 21; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Jones, Indian Shops, Gay Head, Massachusetts - Peabody Essex, Salem, MA, 2006 April 18-October 21; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Ranney, Dragoon with his Charger, The Retrieve - Buffalo Bill Hist CTR, WY, Speed Art Museum, Amon Carter Museum, Phila. Mus. of Art, 2006 May 12-2007 August 26; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Shomei Tomatsu, Cigarette Smoke - SFMOMA, 2006 May 1-August 13; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Eastman Johnson, The Pets - Cantor Center, SAAM, 2006 July 4-October 1; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing loans returned: John Singer Sargent, Man Screaming Study for "Hell" - Museo Thyssen - Bornemisza, Madrid, Petit Palais, Paris, 2006 October 3-2007 May 13; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Breton, Le Colza - Dallas Museum of Art, 2006 October 22-2007 January 7; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Picknell, Road to Concarneau - Vonnoh, Notre Dame de Paris - Naples Museum of Art, Naples, FL, 2007 January 18-May 13; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Daniel Garber, April Landscape - South Room, Green Street - PA Academy of Fine Arts, 2007 January 26-April 8; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Robert Henri, John Sloan - William Merritt Chase, An English Cod - Bruce Museum, 2007 January 17-April 29; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Daniel Garber, Ellicott City, Afternoon - Michener Museum, 2007 January 27-May 6; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Scott, French Village Scene Around a Crucifix - Indiana State Museum, 2007 February 3-June 3; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Kertesz, Quai d'Orleans - NGA, 2007 February 11-May 6; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Chimes, Waterfall - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 2007 February 25-May 6; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Edwin Abbey, Who is Sylvia?... - Brandywine RIver Museum, 2007 March 1-May 20; Series 11 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing loans: Cardiff Loan to Site Santa Fe, 2003 July 26-November 23; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing loans: Childe Hassam, New York Window - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 2004 June 7-September 12; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing loans: Stockholder, Untitled - Weatherspoon Art Museum - Blaffer Gallery, 2005 February 13-2004 November 21; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing loans: Robinson, The Layette, Valley of the Seine - Baltimore Museum of Art, Phoenix Art Museum, Wadsworth Atheneum, 2004 October 16-2005 September 4; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing loans: Gilbert Stuart, George Washington - Met, NGA, 2004 October 18-2005 July 31; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing loans: Willard Metcalf, May Night - Florence Griswold Museum of Art, Old Lyme, CT, 2005 May 1-September 11; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing loans: Clock Conservation and specs, 2005; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing loans: EHG Degas, Cabaret - National Gallery of Art, 2005 March 20-June 12; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing loans: Monet, Willows of Vetheuil - Pissarro, The Louvre, Morning - Linea D'Ombra, Treviso, Italy, 2004 October 22-2005 April 3; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing loans: Degas, Ecole de Danse - Complesso del Vittoriano, Rome, Italy, 2005 October 1-February 7; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing loans: Davies, Before Sunrise - Weber, Scene in the Catskills - Arkansas Art Center, Little Rock, AK, 2004 November 17-2005 January 23; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing loans: Corot, The Moored Boatman, Repose - Museo Thyssen - Bornemisza, Madrid - Ferrara Arte S.P.A., 2005 June 7-2006 January 8; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing loans: Degas, Ecole de Danse - Tate Britain - Phillips Collection, 2005 October 6-2006 May 14; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing loans: Bluemner, Imagination - Whitney Museum, 2005 October 7-2006 February 12; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing loans: Frames to Steve Wilcox, 2004 April-October; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing loans: David Aronson, Crucifixion - Boston University Art Gallery, 2005 February 4-April 3; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing loans: Pissarro, Louvre, Morning, Rainy Weather - Art Gal. NSW, Australia, Nat. Gallery Victoria, 2005 November 18-2006 May 28; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing loans: Roman Ribera Cirera, Cafe Chantant - Fortuny y Carbo, Gypsy Caves, Granada - Albuquerque Museum - Meadows Museum, Dallas, 2005 August 21-2006 February 26; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing loans: Corot, Moored Boatman, Repose - Ferrara Arte S.P.A., 2005 October 9-2006 January 8; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing loans: Childe Hassam, Big Ben - James McNeill Whistler, Battersea Reach, 2005 September 26-2006 January 1; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing loans: Jean Charles Cazin, Rest Before Nightfall - Monticelli, Testing the Fates - Oklahoma City Museum of Art, 2005 September 8-November 27; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing loans: Ann Creager - Henri and Jones, 2005 September-December; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing loans: Gordon Parks, Muslim Black Rally, Muhammad Ali in Training... - Whitechapel Art Gallery - New Art Gallery Walsall, 2005 June 7-2005 November 20; Series 11 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Loan to Fondation de l'Heritage, Lausanne, Switzerland, 2002 June 6-October 20; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing loans returned: William Michael Harnett, Plucked Clean - NGA, Washington DC, 2002 October 13-2003 March 2; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Francis Blackwell Mayer, Leisure and Labor - Richard Norris Brooke, A Pastoral Visit - Edward Lamson Henry, The Old Westover Mansion - VA Historical Society, 2003 February 15-June 8; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Majolica Collection - Columbia Museum of Art, S.C., 1998 June-2003 April; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Frederik Edwin Church, Niagara - P.A. Academy of Fine Art, 2002 June 15-August 30; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Johnathan Lasker, The Realm of the Quaint - MNCars - Kunstsammlung, Dusseldorf, 2003 June 5-2003 November 23; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing loans returned: TBA Carpets from the Clark Collection - Freer and Sackler Galleries, 2003 April 5-June 1; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Fawn (Bronze Sculpture), Elie Nadelman - Whitney Museum, New York, 2003 March 31-July 20; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing loans returned: John Singer Sargent, Simplon Pass - Palazzo dei Diamante - LACMA, CA - Denver Art Museum, 2002 September 29-2003 September 14; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Larry Sultan, Thanksgiving Turkey/Newspaper - Peabody Essex Museum, 2003 June 12-September 21; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Soyer, Waiting Room - Tokyo Station Gallery, Japan - Hiroshima Museum of Art, 2003 August 2-October 26; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Barye, Walking Tiger - BMA - Direct Dimensions/Owens Mills, MD, 2003 December 10; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Eggleston, Memphis - Frist Center, 2003 September 13-2004 January 18; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing loans returned: The Paintings of Joan Mitchell, Salut Tom - Whitney Museum of American Art - Storage Crozier Fine Arts, NYC - Modern Art Museum of Fort Worth, TX, 2002 June 20-2004 January; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Monet: The Seine and the Sea, Vetheuil and Normandy, The Willows - National Gallery of Scotland, 2003 August 6-October 26; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Richard Norris Brooke, A Pastoral Visit - Katonah Museum of Art, 2003 November 9-2004 February 1; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Hans Hofmann, Golden Blaze - Naples Museum of Art, 2003 November-2004 March; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing loans returned: George Inness, Harvest Moon - National Academy of Design, NY - San Diego Museum of Art, 2003 September 17-2004 April 18; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Jean Simeon Chardin, The Scullery Maid - NGA Ottawa - NGA DC - Berlin Venue, 2003 June-2004 January; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Lee Bontecou, Untitled - UCLA Hammer - MOCA, Chicago, 2003 October 4-2004 May 24; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Mariano Fortuny, Gypsy Caves, The Choice of a Model, A Street in Tangiers - Museu Nacional d'Art de Catalunya, Spain, 2003 October 16-2004 February 15; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Sanford Robinson Gifford, The Ruins of the Parthenon - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Amon Carter, TX - NGA, DC, 2003 October 7-2004 September 26; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Kemeys, Jaguar Lovers - Proctor, Stalking Panther - Amon Carter Museum, Fort Worth, TX - Cody, WY, 2003 October 11-2004 October; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Eastman Johnson, The Shelter - Clark Institute - Huntington Library & Gardens, 2004 January 18-2004 August 1; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Heidenerich, Alaska Series: Winter - Berkeley Art Museum, 2004 May 21-October 3; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Sketchbooks to Tom Albro, 2004 September 9-December 31; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Miniatures to Katherine Eirk, 2004 November 1; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing loans returned: Edward Redfield, Mill in Winter - James A. Michener Art Museum, Doylestown, PA, 2004 May 1-2005 January 9; Series 11 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Loans returned: Purchases Refused, 1983-1999; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Loans returned: Gifts Refused/Rescinded, 1896-1999; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Loans returned: Returned TLs, 2002; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Loans returned: Returned TLs, 2001; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Loans returned: Returned TLs, 2000; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Loans returned: Loans to CGA, Returned to Owner, 1999; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Loans returned, 1989-1996; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Loans returned: Gowin, Emmet, Nancy and Dwayne, Danville, VA GSP, 1999 February 10; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Loans returned: Jorg Schmeisser Prints, 2000 May 11; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Loans returned: Jorg Schmeisser - Bridge, 2000 April 13-May 1; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Loans returned: Robert Brown Gallery - William Kentridge - A Nicely Built City, 2001 February; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Loans returned: Bierstadt Photogravure - Wm Talbot, 2001 February 2; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Loans returned: Gilcrease Photogravure, Last of the Buffalo, 2001 February 2; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Loans returned: Claes Oldenburg - Pizza Pie, 2001 November 19; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Loans returned: John E. Dowell, Jr. - 6 Lithos., 2001; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Loans returned: Chihuly, Dale, 2001; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Loans returned: Alexander Calder, Untitled - The Eli and Edythe Broad Collection, 2001 May 25; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Loans returned: Robert Rauschenberg - Haywire II, 2002 January 23; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Loans returned: J. Seward Johnson, Jr. - Eye of the Beholder, 2002 February 12; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Loans returned: McEntee - Gathering Firewood, 2002 November 20; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Loans returned: Frame for Chardin, 2002 February 21; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Loans returned: Roy Lichtenstein - Brushstroke Group, 2002 October 7; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Loans returned: Timothy Egert - Malcolm Morley - Flight of Icarus, 2002 April 23; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Loans returned: Bierstadt Chromolithograph, 2002 December 13; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Loans returned: Pepper, Beverly - In the Pasture - 2 Books, 2002 April 30; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Loans returned: Jackson, Oliver, 2002 July 16; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Loans returned: DC Commission on the Arts - Arty Party I and II, 2002 November 10; Series 11 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Temporary loans returned: David Levinthal - works from Playing with History, 2007 December 10; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Temporary loans returned: Summer, Evan - Copper Plate for Landscape, 2006 August 25; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Temporary loans returned: White, Joe - Rectangle 6, 1967 - Given to American University, 2007 January 18; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Temporary loans returned: Marville, Charles (Brought in for Conservation Purposes), 2007 January 10; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Temporary loans returned: Dunlap, Bill - Fog Lift, 2006 December 11; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Temporary loans returned: Daphnis, Nassos - Three Paintings, 2006 December 11; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Temporary loans returned: Schwartz, Peri - Studio Window XIIA, 2006 August 16; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Temporary loans returned: Jake Ewert - Falling Polar Bear, 2006; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Temporary loans returned: Photographs by Minor White and John Davies on Loan from Sharon Keim, 2006; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Temporary loans returned: King, Charles Bird - Grapes, Peaches, Pears, and Decanter, 2006; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Temporary loans returned: Returned TL's, 2003; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Temporary loans returned: Nutt, Craig - Banana Pepper with Seeds and Fruit, 2003 October; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Temporary loans returned: Gilliam, Sam - Electric, 2005; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Temporary loans returned: Gilliam, Sam - Tapestry, 2002 April-2006 December; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Temporary loans returned: Lent by Mr. and Mrs. Gregory Fazakerly, 2004; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Temporary loans returned: Eva Collins Wallen Foti - Raphaelle Peale - Peeled Oranges - Apples, Nuts, and Fruit, 2004; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Temporary loans returned: Ponte, Rosario - Unsolicited Artwork Return, 2004; Series 11 (Box 119, Folder 17)